Artem Sopilniak

Fullstack developer

Summary

Hello my name is Artem Sopilniak I have completed the training on fullsteck developer. I have several team and individual projects that I have created using such technologies as html, css, javascript, react, redux and node as well as using several libraries that I used to solve problems. During the course I also learned some soft skills such as problem solving, teamwork, finding and using resources that will help me solve the problem. Now thanks to my experience and skills I can make projects qualitatively, fine-tune code and fix bugs almost any.

Contacts

+48 793 392 487 zagrousaspear@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> GitHub

Hard skills

- Html
- Css
- lavaScript
- Redux
- Node
- GitHuh
- Webpack
- Parce
- Rest API
- SASS
 - Responsive graphics

Soft skills

- Troublochootor
- Hard-working
- Attention to
- Autonomous

<u>Ice cream</u>, <u>github link</u> [Html, Css, Parcel]. My first team project where I had a role as frontend developer. My first experience with animations.

Projects

<u>Cinemania</u>, <u>github link</u> [Html, Css, Javascript, parcel, tui-pagination, axios].

My second team project where I also was frontend developer. I was help of team lead to fix bugs and debug code.

Webstudio, github link [Html, Css, Scss].

My first individual projects where I made markup and styles for one page site. This markup contain no interactive interface yet.

Work experience

Customer assistant

Western union | march 2013 - june 2017

- Comunicating with customers and provide them services
- Solving problems which can case with customers

Hotel administrator

Multicolored solar | july 2017 - may 2022

- Providing comfortable environment for customres
- Interacting with workers and customers and meeting their needs

Education

University of computer science Software engineer | september 2009 - june

IT GoIT school

Fullstack developer | september 2022 - july 2023

Languages

Russian - native English - intermediate Japanese - pre-intermediate